

# **Profile**

Front end developer with a strong background in JavaScript, react, and HTML/CSS. I am also well-versed in Git, JQuarry, and Redux. I was responsible for building user interfaces for an e-commerce project. I am confident in pursuing high-quality code in delivering projects on time. As well as having experience in front and development I also have experience in the backend. I have knowledge and noSQL and MySQL.

# **Employment History**

## Bootcamp Projects, University of Arizona, Phoenix

MARCH 2022 - SEPTEMBER 2022

I was responsible for creating well-thought-out web apps and programs. During my time I was able to acquire knowledge in a variety of areas in the process of Web development. I was responsible for working in individual settings as well as group settings. I was confronted with many challenges, from building a fully functional password generator to building an autonomous robotic car that could find its way around any maze. However, one of the most valuable things I got out of these challenges, was mastering the Art of being an independent problem solver and how to find the solution to any challenge thrown at me.

#### Peer Mentor, Arizona State University, Tempe

JULY 2018 - AUGUST 2019

During my time as a peer mentor, I was responsible for helping ASU staff plan the curriculum for summer programs at Arizona State University. I was responsible for working closely with distinguished professors such as Jessica Early and Christina Saidy. My work revolved around mentoring and instructing college freshmen to prepare them for their undergraduate journeys, and to get them closer to being job ready.

## Education

Bachelor's Degree, Arizona State University, Tempe

AUGUST 2017 - MAY 2022

Coding Bootcamp, University of Arizona, Phoenix

MARCH 2022 - AUGUST 2022

#### **Details**

Avondale
United States
4806586214
machadoleandro98@gmail.com

#### Links

Portfolio Page

**GitHub** 

<u>LinkedIn</u>

## **Skills**

HTML & CSS

SQL

**JavaScript** 

Programming

Software Logic

# Languages

**English** 

Spanish

Italian